it's really uncomfortable for people to
have the conversation about insurance
because you are having a conversation
about death about 10 years ago I had a
client come see me whose husband was a
self-employed truck driver at that time
they didn't feel the $15 a month was
worth it for them and he was killed
while he was working so this particular
client had no protection on her mortgage
at that moment I realized that everybody
should know about this type of product
and everybody should be covered because
now she lost her husband and she lost
her home mani lifes mortgage protection
plan is very affordable and it's a small
price to pay if something really big
happens it's so essential for you to do
good to make sure that your loved one at
least they're taken care of
the staff at Manulife they know their
stuff inside and out and with the
process for claims they speed it up they
get it done they don't mess around you
don't have to make a claim that's great
but if you do then at least you have it
I can sleep very well at night knowing
that my clients are protected after they
take the life insurance